Guide to the Tyree Scott Papers
Special Collections, University of Washington Libraries
- NORTHWEST LABOR AND EMPLOYMENT LAW OFFICE (LABOR AND EMPLOYMENT LAW OFFICE) RECORDS, 1961-2005; SERIES 10 (Box-folder 16/32-45/15)
  - Case Files and Legal Papers, 1961-1995; Subseries C (Box-folder 18/33-45/15)
    - Domingo et al. v. New England Fish Company (NEFCO) et al. Pretrial Order-Master File, 1973-1976 (Box-folder 30/1)
    - Domingo et al. v. New England Fish Company (NEFCO) et al. Payroll Register, 1972-1973 (Box-folder 30/2)
    - Domingo et al. v. New England Fish Company (NEFCO) et al. Pretrial Order- Terminations, 1970-1973 (Box-folder 30/3)
    - Domingo et al. v. New England Fish Company (NEFCO) et al. Pretrial Order-Qualifications (Machinists), circa 1970s (Box-folder 30/4)
    - Domingo et al. v. New England Fish Company (NEFCO) et al. Pretrial Order-Hiring for miscellaneous jobs, 1970 (Box-folder 30/5)
    - Domingo et al. v. New England Fish Company (NEFCO) et al. Pretrial Order-Housing Quality, 1970-1995 (Box-folder 30/6)
    - Domingo et al. v. New England Fish Company (NEFCO) et al. Pretrial Order-Messing Pattern, 1973 (Box-folder 30/7)
    - Domingo et al. v. New England Fish Company (NEFCO) et al. Pretrial Order-Food Quality, 1970-1971 (Box-folder 30/8)
    - Domingo et al. v. New England Fish Company (NEFCO) et al. Pretrial Order-Personnel policies, 1976 (Box-folder 30/9)
    - Domingo et al. v. New England Fish Company (NEFCO) et al. Pretrial Order-Nepotism, 1970-1976 (Box-folder 30/10)
    - Domingo et al. v. New England Fish Company (NEFCO) et al. Pretrial Order-Hiring for tender jobs, 1972-1976 (Box-folder 30/11)
    - Domingo et al. v. New England Fish Company (NEFCO) et al. Pretrial Order-Draws, 1971-1972 (Box-folder 30/12)
    - Domingo et al. v. New England Fish Company (NEFCO) et al. Pretrial Order-Centralization, 1970-1974 (Box-folder 30/13)
    - Domingo et al. v. New England Fish Company (NEFCO) et al. Pretrial Order-Policy of Race Discrimination, 1970-1972 (Box-folder 30/14)
    - Domingo et al. v. New England Fish Company (NEFCO) et al. Pretrial Order-Hiring goal (Statistical), Undated (Box-folder 30/15)
    - Domingo et al. v. New England Fish Company (NEFCO) et al. Pretrial Order-Job Segregation (Statistical), Undated (Box-folder 30/16)
    - Domingo et al. v. New England Fish Company (NEFCO) et al. Pretrial Order-Job Segregation (Non-Statistical), 1974 (Box-folder 30/17)
    - Domingo et al. v. New England Fish Company (NEFCO) et al. Pretrial Order-Industry Bckgd, circa 1970s (Box-folder 30/18)
    - Domingo et al. v. New England Fish Company (NEFCO) et al. Pretrial Order-Qualifications (Tender), 1970-1976 (Box-folder 30/19)
    - Domingo et al. v. New England Fish Company (NEFCO) et al. Extra Exhibits (Plaintiffs), 1967-1972 (Box-folder 30/20)
    - Domingo et al. v. New England Fish Company (NEFCO) et al. Rebuttal Exhibit (Plaintiffs), 1970-1976 (Box-folder 30/21)
    - Domingo et al. v. New England Fish Company (NEFCO) et al. Defendant's Exhibits, Part 1 of 2, circa 1970s (Box-folder 30/22)
    - Domingo et al. v. New England Fish Company (NEFCO) et al. Defendant's Exhibits, Part 2 of 2, circa 1970s (Box-folder 30/23)
    - Domingo et al. v. New England Fish Company (NEFCO) et al. Interrogatory 26, 1970-1975 (Box-folder 30/24)
    - Domingo et al. v. New England Fish Company (NEFCO) et al. Documents which were not used. Part 1 of 3., 1967-1975 (Box-folder 30/25)
    - Domingo et al. v. New England Fish Company (NEFCO) et al. Documents which were not used. Part 2 of 3., 1970-1976 (Box-folder 30/26)
    - Domingo et al. v. New England Fish Company (NEFCO) et al. Documents which were not used. Part 3 of 3, 1970-1976 (Box-folder 30/27)
    - Domingo et al. v. New England Fish Company (NEFCO) et al. Defendant's First Interrogatories to Plaintiffs and Amended Answers, 1975-1976 (Box-folder 30/28)
    - Domingo et al. v. New England Fish Company (NEFCO) et al. First Interrogatories to Defendants, 1974 (Box-folder 30/29)
    - Domingo et al. v. New England Fish Company (NEFCO) et al. Master Interrogatory 26 Chatham, 1970-1972 (Box-folder 30/30)
    - Domingo et al. v. New England Fish Company (NEFCO) et al.Witness File- Donald Mayall, 1970-1973 (Box-folder 30/31)
    - Domingo et al. v. New England Fish Company (NEFCO) et al. Witness File-Shirley Smith, 1973 (Box-folder 30/32)
    - Domingo et al. v. New England Fish Company (NEFCO) et al. Witness File- C. Reid Rogers, 1973-1975 (Box-folder 30/33)
    - Domingo et al. v. New England Fish Company (NEFCO) et al. Witness File- Patricia Jaspar, 1976 (Box-folder 30/34)
    - Domingo et al. v. New England Fish Company (NEFCO) et al. Witness File- Adolph Lewis, 1975 (Box-folder 30/35)
    - Domingo et al. v. New England Fish Company (NEFCO) et al. Witness File- Galen Biery, 1976 (Box-folder 30/36)
    - Domingo et al. v. New England Fish Company (NEFCO) et al. Witness File- Tony Gregory, 1976 (Box-folder 30/37)
    - Domingo et al. v. New England Fish Company (NEFCO) et al. Witness File 1- Lillian Sturrock, 1976 (Box-folder 31/1)
    - Domingo et al. v. New England Fish Company (NEFCO) et al. Witness File 2- Lilian Sturrock, 1974-1975 (Box-folder 31/2)
    - Domingo et al. v. New England Fish Company (NEFCO) et al. Witness File- Ronald Ames, 1976 (Box-folder 31/3)
    - Domingo et al. v. New England Fish Company (NEFCO) et al. Witness File- Bill McGrath, 1976 (Box-folder 31/4)
    - Domingo et al. v. New England Fish Company (NEFCO) et al. Witness File- Arnold Gibson, 1976 (Box-folder 31/5)
    - Domingo et al. v. New England Fish Company (NEFCO) et al. Witness File- Gretchen Wagner, 1976 (Box-folder 31/6)
    - Domingo et al. v. New England Fish Company (NEFCO) et al. Witness file - Laurel Bland, 1975-1976 (Box-folder 31/7)
    - Domingo et al. v. New England Fish Company (NEFCO) et al. Deposition of Jack Bunnell, 1979 (Box-folder 31/8)
    - Domingo et al. v. New England Fish Company (NEFCO) et al. Witness File- Julia Laranang, 1976 (Box-folder 31/9)
    - Domingo et al. v. New England Fish Company (NEFCO) et al. Witness File- Robert Flanagan, 1974 (Box-folder 31/10)
    - Domingo et al. v. New England Fish Company (NEFCO) et al. Witness File- Chip Hoins, circa 1970s (Box-folder 31/11)
    - Domingo et al. v. New England Fish Company (NEFCO) et al. Witness File- Gene Silberberg, 1968-1978 (Box-folder 31/12)
    - Domingo et al. v. New England Fish Company (NEFCO) et al. Witness File- Macabeo, Foster, 1976 (Box-folder 31/13)
    - Domingo et al. v. New England Fish Company (NEFCO) et al. Miscellaneous documents- Not produced by NEFCO, 1957-1972 (Box-folder 31/14)
    - Domingo et al. v. New England Fish Company (NEFCO) et al. Exhibits- Cannery Chart of Accounts II, 1970-1975 (Box-folder 31/15)
    - Cannery Cases/Canning Machinery, 1975 (Box-folder 31/16)
    - Domingo et al. v. New England Fish Company (NEFCO) et al. NEFCO Housing Document File Search, 1977 (Box-folder 31/17)
    - Domingo et al. v. New England Fish Company (NEFCO) et al. Fisherman Issue- Documents from Alaska Legal Services, 1969-1976 (Box-folder 31/18)
    - Domingo et al. v. New England Fish Company (NEFCO) et al. Miscellaneous Documents- Shipped from Uganik and Chatham (1 of 2), 1969-1974 (Box-folder 31/19)
    - Domingo et al. v. New England Fish Company (NEFCO) et al. Miscellaneous Documents- Shipped from Uganik and Chatham (2 of 2), 1969-1974 (Box-folder 31/20)
    - Domingo et al. v. New England Fish Company (NEFCO) et al. Miscellaneous Documents from Egegik and Pederson Point, 1969-1974 (Box-folder 31/21)
    - Domingo et al. v. New England Fish Company (NEFCO) et al. Agreement: Bristol Bay resident cannery, Local 46 workers, 1975 (Box-folder 31/22)
    - Domingo et al. v. New England Fish Company (NEFCO) et al. NEFCO Exhibits, maps of cannery, circa 1970s and 1980s (Box-folder 31/23)
    - Domingo et al. v. New England Fish Company (NEFCO) et al. Exhibits- Cannery charts of account, 1972 (Box-folder 31/24)
    - Domingo et al. v. New England Fish Company (NEFCO) et al. Uganik Bay Settlement Sheets, 1971 (Box-folder 31/25)
    - Domingo et al. v. New England Fish Company (NEFCO) et al. Fishermen Documents, 1970-1974 (Box-folder 31/26)
    - Domingo et al. v. New England Fish Company (NEFCO) et al. Fish Catch Summaries- Egegik, 1971-1974 (Box-folder 31/27)
    - Domingo et al. v. New England Fish Company (NEFCO) et al. Time Sheets/ Double Job Holders (1 of 2), 1970-1975 (Box-folder 32/1)
    - Domingo et al. v. New England Fish Company (NEFCO) et al. Time Sheets/ Double Job Holders (2 of 2), 1970-1975 (Box-folder 32/2)
    - Domingo et al. v. New England Fish Company (NEFCO) et al. Chatham Settlement Sheets A-L, 1973 (Box-folder 32/3)
    - Domingo et al. v. New England Fish Company (NEFCO) et al. Chatham Settlement Sheets A-K, 1971 (Box-folder 32/4)
    - Domingo et al. v. New England Fish Company (NEFCO) et al. Chatham Settlement Sheets L-Z, 1971 (Box-folder 32/5)
    - Domingo et al. v. New England Fish Company (NEFCO) et al. Chatham Settlement Sheets A-I, 1972 (Box-folder 32/6)
    - Domingo et al. v. New England Fish Company (NEFCO) et al. Uganik Settlement Sheets, 1973 (Box-folder 32/7)
    - Domingo et al. v. New England Fish Company (NEFCO) et al. Egegik Settlement Sheets, 1971 (Box-folder 32/8)
    - Domingo et al. v. New England Fish Company (NEFCO) et al. Egegik Settlement Sheets (Selected), 1972 (Box-folder 32/9)
    - Domingo et al. v. New England Fish Company (NEFCO) et al. Egegik Settlement Sheets (Selected), 1973-1974 (Box-folder 32/10)
    - Domingo et al. v. New England Fish Company (NEFCO) et al. Chatam Settlement Sheets (Selected), 1973 (Box-folder 32/11)
    - Domingo et al. v. New England Fish Company (NEFCO) et al. Chatham Settlement Sheets J-Z (Selected), 1972 (Box-folder 32/12)
    - Domingo et al. v. New England Fish Company (NEFCO) et al. Ugunik Settlement Sheets K-Z (Selected), 1972 (Box-folder 32/13)
    - Domingo et al. v. New England Fish Company (NEFCO) et al. Pederson Point Settlement Sheets (Selected), 1975 (Box-folder 32/14)
    - Domingo et al. v. New England Fish Company (NEFCO) et al. Uganik Settlement Sheets A-Z (Selected), 1974 (Box-folder 32/15)
    - Domingo et al. v. New England Fish Company (NEFCO) et al. Pederson Points Settlement Sheets (Selected), 1974 (Box-folder 32/16)
    - Domingo et al. v. New England Fish Company (NEFCO) et al. Pederson Point Settlement Sheets (Selected), 1973 (Box-folder 32/17)
    - Domingo et al. v. New England Fish Company (NEFCO) et al. Pederson Point Settlement Sheets A-G (Selected), 1971 (Box-folder 32/18)
    - Domingo et al. v. New England Fish Company (NEFCO) et al. Uganik Settlement Sheets (Selected), 1975 (Box-folder 32/19)
    - Domingo et al. v. New England Fish Company (NEFCO) et al. Pederson Point Settlement Sheets (Selected), 1972 (Box-folder 32/20)
    - Domingo et al. v. New England Fish Company (NEFCO) et al. Documents Produced, Part 1 of 2, 1966-1973 (Box-folder 32/21)
    - Doming et al. v. New England Fish Company (NEFCO) et al. Documents Produced, Part 2 of 2., 1970-1973 (Box-folder 32/22)
    - Domingo et al. v. New England Fish Company (NEFCO) et al. Documents Produced-Shipward sign-on sheet, 1972 (Box-folder 32/23)
    - Domingo et al. v. New England Fish Company (NEFCO) et al. Uganik Bay Settlement Sheets A-J (Selected), 1972 (Box-folder 33/1)
    - Domingo et al. v. New England Fish Company (NEFCO) et al. Egegik Settlement Sheets (Selected), 1970 (Box-folder 33/2)
    - Domingo et al. v. New England Fish Company (NEFCO) et al. Pederson Point Settlement Sheets O-Z (Selected), 1971 (Box-folder 33/3)
    - Domingo et al. v. New England Fish Company (NEFCO) et al. Pederson Point Settlement Sheets H-N (Selected), 1971 (Box-folder 33/4)
    - Domingo et al. v. New England Fish Company (NEFCO) et al. Settlement Sheets of Employees with Double Jobs, Part 1 of 2, 1971-1975 (Box-folder 33/5)
    - Domingo et al. v. New England Fish Company (NEFCO) et al. Settlement Sheets of Employees with Double Jobs, Part 2 of 2, 1971-1975 (Box-folder 33/6)
    - Carpenter v. NEFCO-Fidalgo, Deposition of Shirley Smith, 1979 (Box-folder 33/7)
    - New England Fish Company (NEFCO) et al. Carpenter v. NEFCO-Fidalgo, Interrogatories, 1974 (Box-folder 33/8)
    - Carpenter v. New England Fish Company (NEFCO) et al. Fidalgo, Deposition of Arnold Gibson, circa 1970s and 1980s (Box-folder 33/9)
    - Carpenter v. New England Fish Company (NEFCO) et al. Fidalgo, Gary Latham- Witness File, 1979 (Box-folder 33/10)
    - Carpenter v. New England Fish Company (NEFCO) et al. Fidalgo, Interrogatories, 1976 (Box-folder 33/11)
    - Carpenter v. New England Fish Company (NEFCO) et al. Fidalgo, Deposition of Larry Benjamin, 1979 (Box-folder 33/12)
    - Carpenter v. New England Fish Company (NEFCO) et al. Fidalgo, Miscellaneous Trial Exhibits, 1956-1979 (Box-folder 33/13)
    - Carpenter v. New England Fish Company (NEFCO) et al. Fidalgo, Interrogatories, 1975 (Box-folder 33/14)
    - Carpenter v. New England Fish Company (NEFCO) et al. Fidalgo, Deposition of Lane Rawlins, 1979 (Box-folder 33/15)
    - Carpenter v. New England Fish Company (NEFCO) et al. Fidalgo, Deposition of Gary Latham, 1979 (Box-folder 33/16)
    - Carpenter v. New England Fish Company (NEFCO) et al. Fidalgo, Shirley Smith, 1970 (Box-folder 33/17)
    - Carpenter v. New England Fish Company (NEFCO) et al. Fidalgo, Lane Rawlins, background material for deposition, 1970-1977 (Box-folder 33/18)
    - Carpenter v. New England Fish Company (NEFCO) et al. Fidalgo, working file, second motion to dismiss, 1970 (Box-folder 33/19)
    - Atonio v. Wards Cove Packing Co., Documents-Ekuk Housing Reports, 1970-1977 (Box-folder 33/20)
    - Atonio v. Wards Cove Packing Co., Discovery Missing Items: Lists of Outstanding Documents, 1976 (Box-folder 33/21)
    - Atonio v. Wards Cove Packing Co., Extra Copies of Exhibits, 1969-1978 (Box-folder 33/22)
    - Atonio v. Wards Cove Packing Co. Segregation Charts FINAL & XEROX, circa 1970s and 1980s (Box-folder 33/23)
    - Atonio v. Wards Cove Packing Co., Letter from Bowman re ACWA Report; Other Documents re APF Affirmative Action, 1973-1975 (Box-folder 33/24)
    - Atonio v. Wards Cove Packing Co., Ekuk-Hiring Cannery Workers, 1971 (Box-folder 33/25)
    - Atonio v. Wards Cove Packing Co., Bumble Bee-Local 37 Hiring; Hiring Women Outside the Hall, 1973 (Box-folder 33/26)
    - Atonio v. Wards Cove Packing Co., Letters re APF Affirmative Action, 1973 (Box-folder 33/27)
    - Atonio v. Wards Cove Packing Co., Letters from Hirstel re Negotiation, 1970-1976 (Box-folder 34/1)
    - Atonio v. Wards Cove Packing Co., Ekuk-Recruitment in Villages; Soliciting Returnees, 1969-1970 (Box-folder 34/2)
    - Atonio V. Wards Cove Packing Co., Ekuk-Recruiting Tendermen; Preference to Concordia, 1971-1972 (Box-folder 34/3)
    - Atonio v. Wards Cove Packing Co., Ekuk-Crew Lists; "Native" Designations and "White", 1969-1971 (Box-folder 34/4)
    - Atonio v. Wards Cove Packing Co., Alitak-Aff Action; Bunkhouses; "Integrating" a Messhall, 1974-1975 (Box-folder 34/5)
    - Atonio v. Wards Cove Packing Co., Ekuk-Crew Lists; Recruiting Mach, Rad Operator, Tenderman, 1973 (Box-folder 34/6)
    - Atonio v. Wards Cove Packing Co., Ekuk-Recruiting Tendermen; Let-on Hiring CW's in AK and Other Jobs in Lower 48., 1970 (Box-folder 34/7)
    - Atonio v. Wards Cove Packing Co., Hiring Store Helper; and Engineer (With Minimal Exp)-Ekuk, 1975 (Box-folder 34/8)
    - Atonio v. Wards Cove Packing Co., Letter to Prospective Employee at Concordia, 1974 (Box-folder 34/9)
    - Atonio v. Wards Cove Packing Co., Hiring Pam Ekern; Recruitment at Concordia, 1971-1972 (Box-folder 34/10)
    - Atonio v. Wards Cove Packing Co., Ekuk-Recruitment at Native Villages, 1972-1973 (Box-folder 34/11)
    - Atonio v. Wards Cove Packing Co., Port Vailey-Crew Lists for AFU, and Machinist Union, 1970-1975 (Box-folder 34/12)
    - Atonio v. Wards Cove Packing Co., Ekuk Recruitment of Port Engineers, and Cooks, 1971 (Box-folder 34/13)
    - Atonio v. Wards Cove Packing Co., Ekuk-Word-of-Mouth; Recruitment in Villages, 1974-1975 (Box-folder 34/14)
    - Atonio v. Wards Cove Packing Co., Kodiak-Recruitment from White Colleges; Machinist Application by Non-Whites, 1971-1974 (Box-folder 34/15)
    - Atonio v. Wards Cove Packing Co. - Sujiko Agreement, 1969 (Box-folder 34/16)
    - Atonio v. Wards Cove Packing Co. Letter to Prospective Fishermen [$8.75 Room/Board]; Letter from A.W. Brindle re Housing Assignments; CWF Fish Boat Charter (Sex-Race-use women instead of natives), 1971 (Box-folder 34/17)
    - Atonio v. Wards Cove Packing Co. Letter from A.W. Brindle re Housing Assignments, and New Bunkhouse at Red Salmon, 1970 (Box-folder 34/18)
    - Atonio v. Wards Cove Packing Co. Letter from Hirstel re Negotiations [Includes washers & dryers]; Letter from A.W. Brindle re Prohibiting Handguns, 1970 (Box-folder 34/19)
    - Atonio v. Wards Cove Packing Co. Chignik - Hiring Mach Helper; Letter to Mach Union, 1973 (Box-folder 34/20)
    - Atonio v. Wards Cove Packing Co. Ekuk - AFU Crew List; Nepotism among co fishermen, 1970 (Box-folder 34/21)
    - Atonio v. Wards Cove Packing Co.Letter from A.W. Brindle re Need to build better bunkhouses for fishermen at Egegik [afraid they will go to APA], 1971 (Box-folder 34/22)
    - Atonio v. Wards Cove Packing Co. Recommendations by Egegik fishermen [includes housing], 1971 (Box-folder 34/23)
    - Atonio v. Wards Cove Packing Co. List of CWF Mortgaged Fish Boats, 1971 (Box-folder 34/24)
    - Atonio v. Wards Cove Packing Co. Letter from A.W. Brindle re Alaska Human Rights request, 1974 (Box-folder 34/25)
    - Atonio v. Wards Cove Packing Co. Bumble Bee to Change Independent Fish; substandard CW Bunkhouse at Ekuk, 1973 (Box-folder 34/26)
    - Atonio v. Wards Cove Packing Co. Letter to Superintendents from Gilbert & Brindlere Conciliation Agreement, circa 1970s (Box-folder 34/27)
    - Atonio v. Wards Cove Packing Co.Bumble Bee correspondence re Race Labelling, Segregation, Company Policy, 1976-1978 (Box-folder 34/28)
    - Atonio v. Wards Cove Packing Co. Bumble Bee capital expenditures re messhall segregation, race labelling, job hazards and conditions, and corporate policy on investment in non-productive assets, 1970-1977 (Box-folder 34/29)
    - Atonio v. Wards Cove Packing Co. Bumble Bee documents of race labelling of employees, bunkhouses, cooks, 1972 (Box-folder 34/30)
    - Atonio v. Wards Cove Packing Co. Bumble Bee purchase orders, OSHA report, terminations, 1970-1976 (Box-folder 34/31)
    - Atonio v. Wards Cove Packing Co. Bumble Bee quality control, bunkhouse description, bunkhouse assignments, race labelling, 1976 (Box-folder 34/32)
    - Atonio v. Wards Cove Packing Co. Bumble Bee Journal entries and statements re race labelling, 1970 (Box-folder 34/33)
    - Atonio v. Wards Cove Packing Co. AWB General Correspondence 1968-9 race labelling, terminations, recruitment, 1968-1969 (Box-folder 34/34)
    - Atonio v. Wards Cove Packing Co. AWB General Correspondence 1968 Recruitment of cannery workers from American Methodist University (AMU) & University of Alaska (Box-folder 34/35)
    - Atonio v. Wards Cove Packing Co. Craig Cannery, minor fisherman "iron chink," bareboat charter, 1972 (Box-folder 34/36)
    - Atonio v. Wards Cove Packing Co. Exhibits - Racial Comments, 1971 (Box-folder 34/37)
    - Thomas G.Carpenter, et al. v. NEFCO-Fidalgo Packing Co Court Stipulation and letter requesting interview, 1979 (Box-folder 34/38)
    - Atonio v. Wards Cove Packing Co. Documents - duplicates and missing, 1970-1976 (Box-folder 34/39)
    - Local 37 ILWU Dispatches - All Canneries, 1978 (Box-folder 34/40)
    - Atonio v. Wards Cove Packing Co. Exhibits - Recruitment, 1970-1973 (Box-folder 34/41)
    - Atonio v. Wards Cove Packing Co. Delegate's reports for Red Salmon, Ketchikan, Alitak, Bumble Bee; Super's response; Petition for better facilities at Ketchikan; Report re poor messing facilities, bedding, housing, washers. Also requests separate bunkhou, 1970-1974 (Box-folder 34/42)
    - Atonio v. Wards Cove Packing Co. Alitak - Soliciting Local 37 returnees; Letter from Fred Wong re housing, messing, "the opposition;" etc., 1972-1975 (Box-folder 34/43)
    - Atonio v. Wards Cove Packing Co. Ketchitkan - termination letters; AFU re better showers, washers & dryers for tendermen, 1971-1975 (Box-folder 34/44)
    - Atonio v. Wards Cove Packing Co. Letter re termination of all company fishermen & catches; Lists of company; Lists of Independent Fishermen, catches; Lists of set netters, catches; Letter from AFU protesting terminations, 1972-1974 (Box-folder 34/45)
    - Atonio v. Wards Cove Packing Co. Kenai Cannery; applications, recruitment, nepotism, race labelling, 1972 (Box-folder 34/46)
    - Atonio v. Wards Cove Packing Co. General Memorandum 1966, AWB Correspondence; Wards Cove ledger sheets, race labelling, 1966-1970 (Box-folder 34/47)
    - Atonio v. Wards Cove Packing Co. Alitak interoffice communications; race labelling, bareboat charter, 1970 (Box-folder 34/48)
    - Atonio v. Wards Cove Packing Co. Alitak termination notices & recruitment letters, 1970 (Box-folder 34/49)
    - Atonio v. Wards Cove Packing Co. Alitak grocery invoices; race labelling, food quality, 1970 (Box-folder 34/50)
    - Atonio v. Wards Cove Packing Co. Ekuk cannery worker list, application, recruitment, 1970 (Box-folder 34/51)
    - Atonio v. Wards Cove Packing Co. Ekuk bunkhouse assignments, nepotism, word of mouth recruitment, race labelling, quality control training, 1969 (Box-folder 34/52)
    - Atonio v. Wards Cove Packing Co. Ekuk word of mouth recruitment, race labelling, health, sanitation & safety deficiencies, 1970 (Box-folder 34/53)
    - Atonio v. Wards Cove Packing Co. Ekuk bunkhouse assignments, rules, EEOC Affirmative Action Agreement, terminations, race labelling, 1969 (Box-folder 34/54)
    - Atonio v. Wards Cove Packing Co. Ekuk bunkhouse five, worker list, union correspondence, delegate reports, bunkhouse assignments, application letters, 1976 (Box-folder 34/55)
    - Atonio v. Wards Cove Packing Co. Ekuk correspondence - recruitment, nepotism, 1976 (Box-folder 34/56)
    - Atonio v. Wards Cove Packing Co. Ekuk recruitment, nepotism, race labelling, 1970 (Box-folder 34/57)
    - Atonio v. Wards Cove Packing Co. Red Salmon correspondence re race labelling, housing quality, food quality, working conditions, 1973 (Box-folder 34/58)
    - Atonio v. Wards Cove Packing Co. Red Salmon correspondence re race labelling,food quality, 1961 (Box-folder 34/59)
    - Atonio v. Wards Cove Packing Co. Red Salmon correspondence re race labelling, intent, segregation, hiring preferences, job qualifications, 1970-1971 (Box-folder 34/60)
    - Atonio v. Wards Cove Packing Co: Red Salmon correspondence re race labelling, nepotisms hiring, job qualifications, promotions, bunkhouse, 1971 (Box-folder 34/61)
    - Atonio v. Wards Cove Packing Co. Red Salmon Correspondence re: race labelling, recruiting, 1971 (Box-folder 34/62)
    - Atonio v. Wards Cove Packing Co. Red Salmon Correspondence re: hiring, race label, food quality, messhall, recruiting, 1971 (Box-folder 34/63)
    - Atonio v. Wards Cove Packing Co. Red Salmon Correspondence, 1972 (Box-folder 34/64)
    - Atonio v. Wards Cove Packing Co. Red Salmon Correspondence re: race labelling, job earnings, job qualification, nepotism, hiring, housing quality, 1970-1973 (Box-folder 34/65)
    - Atonio v. Wards Cove Packing Co Red Salmon Ekuk Correspondence re: job qualifications and earnings, race labelling, food quality, nepotism, race identification of job applications, 1970-1971 (Box-folder 34/66)
    - Atonio v. Wards Cove Packing Co Red Salmon Correspondence re: race labelling, hiring practices, nepotism, job applications, etc., 1971-1978 (Box-folder 34/67)